Guide to the Stephen M. Cabrinety Collection in the History of Microcomputing, ca. 1975-1995
Department of Special Collections
- Documentation, Subseries 4
  - VIC 20 programmer's reference guide / A. Finkel ... [et al.]. 1st ed. Indianapolis, Ind.: Commodore Business Machines and Howard W. Sams, c1982. xiv, 289 p.: ill.; 22 cm., 1982 (Box 228, Folder 9)
  - Wasteland Survival Guide, 1987 (Box 228, Folder 10)
  - Watson, William Scott. 55 advanced computer programs in BASIC / by Wm. Scott Watson. Fifty-five advanced computer programs in BASIC. Blue Ridge Summit, Pa.: Tab Books, c1981. 252 p.; 22 cm. ISBN: 0830612955 (pbk.): $9.95, 1981 (Box 228, Folder 11)
  - The Way of the Avatar: a guide to Ultima IV, n.d. (Box 228, Folder 12)
  - Whitmore, Kim. Golden Path: a novella. Firebird, 1986 (Box 228, Folder 13)
  - Wico Command Control joystick manual, n.d. (Box 228, Folder 14)
  - Windows Sources.--Vol. 2, no. 6, 1994 June (Box 228, Folder 15)
  - Wired.--Vol. 2, no. 6, 1994 June (Box 228, Folder 16)
  - Word Wizard Parents' Guide, 1984 (Box 228, Folder 17)
  - Worth, Don D. Beneath Apple ProDOS / by Don D. Worth and Pieter M. Lechner. Chatsworth, Calif.: Quality Software, c1987 June. 270 p. in various pagings, [1] folded leaf: ill.; 22 cm., 1987 (Box 228, Folder 18)
  - WPS-80 Operator's Guide, Version 1.0, 1984 May (Box 228, Folder 19)
  - Young, Thomas, 1934- Linear systems and digital signal processing / Thomas Young. Englewood Cliffs, NJ: Prentice-Hall, c1985. x, 357 p.: ill.; 24 cm., 1985 (Box 228, Folder 20)
  - Zak McKracken hint book, n.d. (Box 228, Folder 21)
  - Zero.--No. 20, 1991 Aug. (Box 228, Folder 22)
  - SubLogic Cash Track Home Accounting System ver. 1.1 Dealer copy / Promotional copy manual, n.d. (Box 228, Folder 23)
  - IBM Writing Assistant ver. 1.01 manual, n.d. (Box 228, Folder 24)
  - IBM Graphing Assistant ver. 1.01 manual, n.d. (Box 228, Folder 25)
  - IBM Filing Assistant ver. 1.01 manual, n.d. (Box 228, Folder 26)
  - IBM Personal Computer Hardware Reference Library: BASIC by Microsoft Corp. [Basic / by Microsoft Corp. 1st ed., rev. Boca Raton, Fla.: IBM Corp., 1983. 1 v. (loose-leaf); 23 cm. IBM Personal Computer PCjr hardware reference library. International Business Machines Corporation.Microsoft. "6322881." ], 1983 Oct.. (Box 228, Folder 27)
  - IBM Personal Computer Software Library: Macro Assembler [Macro assembler. Personal computer software library. 1st ed. Boca Raton, Fla.: IBM, 1982- 1 v. (loose-leaf); 24 cm. Personal computer computer language seriesIssued in a case. On case: Personal computer software library. "6172234."], 1983 Oct.. (Box 228, Folder 28)
  - IBM reporting assistant machine readable data file.Reporting assistant. Version 1.00. Boca Raton, Fla.: IBM, c1984. program files (IBM-PC, PC-XT) on 1 computer disk; 5 1/4 in. + 1 manual + 1 quick reference card. IBM assistant seriesNOTES: system requirements: 128 KB memory; 1 double-sided disk drive; monochrome or color display; parallel or serial printer; DOS 1.1 or later., 1984 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - IBM Personal Computer Hardware Reference Library: BASIC by Microsoft Corp. machine readable data file.[Basic / by Microsoft Corp. 1st ed., rev. Boca Raton, Fla.: IBM Corp., 1983. 1 computer cartridge; 1 v. (loose-leaf); 23 cm. IBM Personal Computer PCjr hardware reference library. International Business Machines Corporation.Microsoft. "6024101." ], 1984 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - Disk operating system machine-readable data file / by Microsoft Corp. DOS. The I.B.M. personal computer DOS. Version 2.10. Baca Raton, Fla.: IBM, 1983. 2 program biles (IBM PC) on 2 computer disks; 5 1/4 in. + 1 reference manual (loose-leaf; 23 cm) + 1 user's guide (92 p. in various paginations: ill.; 22 cm.) + 1 quick reference card. IBM Personal Computer computer language series. "First edition September 1983". Includes index. On spine: DOS. Contents: File 1. DOS (#1502341). -- File 2. DOS supplemental programs (#1502342). System requirements: 64K; 128K for fixed disk., 1983 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - Sony Corporation. CP/M Operating System part 1 machine readable data file. Version 2.2, release 2.1 Microcomputer SMC-70. Includes supplement for release 2.0, 1982 (Box 229, Folder 4)
  - Sony Corporation. CP/M Operating System part 2 machine readable data file. Version 2.2, release 2.1 Microcomputer SMC-70. Includes supplement for release 2.0, 1982 (Box 229, Folder 5)
  - AT&T. UNIX System V Release 3: programmer's reference manual / AT&T.1 v. (various pagings); 24 cm., 1986 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - PC Blast II computer file Rev. 8.1. Baton Rouge, La.: Communications Research Group, c1987. Program files (IBM-PC) on 2 computer disks; 5 1/4 in. + 1 operator's manual + 1 concepts and reference manual. Communications Research Group. "Communications software for micros, minis, and mainframes." Title from label. System requirements: IBM PC or compatible; 360K; MS-DOS., 1987 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - VCN ExecuVision machine-readable data file: the presentation graphics program. V.C.N. ExecuVision. Cambridge, MA: Visual Communication Network, c1983. 2 computer disks; 5 1/4 in. + 1 loose-leaf manual (ca. 421 p.) + 1 menu-summary card. System requirements: Personal Computer; 256K; DOS disk 2.0 or 2.1; two double-sided disk drives, PC color/graphics monitor and monitor adaptor, parallel interface printer recommended., 1983 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - The COMPAQ personal computer DOS [machine-readable data file] Version 1.11 [Houston, Tex.]: COMPAQ Computer Corporation, 1983. 1 program file on 1 computer disk: sd; 5 1/4 in. + 1 operations guide + 1 DOS reference guide + 1 BASIC reference guide., 1983 (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - IBM Personal Computer Hardware Reference Library: Guide to Operations IBM PCjr. Boca Raton, Florida: IBM, 1983. 1 program manual + MultiDisplay card booklet., 1983 (Box 230, Folder 1)
  - Carbon copy plus computer file Version 5.0. Newport Beach, CA: Meridian Technology, 1988. program files (IBM PC) on 1 computer disk; 3 1/2 in. + 1 user's manual. Summary: Carbon copy plus is a remote control/communications program that allows you to access, observe, and control the operation of another PC over a normal telephone line. System requirements: IBM PC, PCXT, PCAT, PS/2 or compatible; MS-DOS or PC-DOS 2.0 or later; 256K; Hayes or Hayes compatible modems., 1988 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - TRS-80 Color Computer Electronic Book, n.d. (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - IBM 5100 Portable Computer maintenance library manual, 1976 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - [Broderbund Software] The Toy Shop refill pack, 1986 (Box 230, Folder 5)
  - IBM PCjr Carrying case operating instructions, n.d. (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - Communications Week.--No. 628, 1996 Sept. 16 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - Communications Week.--No. 629, 1996 Sept. 18 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - Communications Week.--No. 630, 1996 Sept. 23 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - Communications Week.--No. 631, 1996 Sept. 30 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - Communications Week.--No. 632, 1996 Oct. 7 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - Communications Week.--No. 635, 1996 Oct. 28 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - Communications Week.--No. 636, 1996 Nov. 4 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - Communications Week.--No. 638, 1996 Nov. 18 (Box 231, Folder 8)
  - Communications Week.--No. 639, 1996 Nov. 25 (Box 231, Folder 9)
  - Communications Week.--No. 640, 1996 Dec. 2 (Box 231, Folder 10)
  - Communications Week.--No. 641, 1996 Dec. 9 (Box 231, Folder 11)
  - Communications Week.--No. 642, 1996 Dec. 16 (Box 231, Folder 12)
  - Computer Currents.--Vol. 10, no. 5 [2 copies], 1995 May (Box 231, Folder 13)
  - Computer Currents.--Vol. 8, no. 12 [2 copies], 1993 Dec. (Box 231, Folder 14)
  - Computer Currents.--Vol. 9, no. 1 [2 copies], 1994 Jan. (Box 231, Folder 15)
  - Computer Currents.--Vol. 9, no. 2 [2 copies], 1994 Feb. (Box 231, Folder 16)
  - Computer Currents.--Vol. 9, no. 8 [2 copies], 1994 Aug. (Box 231, Folder 17)
  - Computer Reseller News.--No. 696, 1996 Aug. 12 (Box 231, Folder 18)
  - Computer Reseller News.--No. 700 [2 copies], 1996 Sept. 9 (Box 231, Folder 19)
  - Computer Reseller News.--No. 701 [includes Benchmarks: Exclusive Product and Trend Research for Resellers, a supplement to], 1996 Sept. 16 (Box 231, Folder 20)
  - Computer Reseller News.--No. 704 [2 copies], 1996 Oct. 7 (Box 231, Folder 21)
  - Computer Reseller News.--No. 705 [includes Special Report: The outlook on monitors, second of two parts], 1996 Oct. 14 (Box 231, Folder 22)
  - Computer Reseller News.--No. 707 [includes: Careers: Employment opportunities and hiring strategies, a special edition of], 1996 Oct. 28 (Box 231, Folder 23)
  - Computer Reseller News.--No. 710 [2 copies], 1996 Nov. 17 (Box 231, Folder 24)
  - Computer Retail Week.--Vol. 6, no. 145, 1996 Sept. 9 (Box 231, Folder 25)
  - Computer Retail Week.--Vol. 6, no. 146, 1996 Sept. 16 (Box 231, Folder 26)
  - Computer Retail Week.--Vol. 6, no. 147, 1996 Sept. 23 (Box 231, Folder 27)
  - Computer Retail Week.--Vol. 6, no. 149, 1996 Oct. 7 (Box 231, Folder 28)
  - Computer Retail Week.--Vol. 6, no. 150, 1996 Oct. 14 (Box 231, Folder 29)
  - Computer Retail Week.--Vol. 6, no. 151, 1996 Oct. 21 (Box 231, Folder 30)
  - Computer Retail Week.--Vol. 6, no. 152, 1996 Oct. 28 (Box 231, Folder 31)
  - Computer Retail Week.--Vol. 6, no. 153, 1996 Nov. 4 (Box 231, Folder 32)
  - Computer Retail Week.--Vol. 6, no. 155, 1996 Nov. 18 (Box 231, Folder 33)
  - Computer Shopper.--Vol. 11, no. 12, issue 141, 1991 Dec. (Box 231, Folder 34)
  - Computer Shopper.--Vol. 12, no. 1, issue 142, 1992 Jan. (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Computer Shopper.--Vol. 12, no. 2, issue 143, 1992 Feb. (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Computer Shopper.--Vol. 12, no. 3, issue 144, 1992 Mar. (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Computer Shopper.--Vol. 12, no. 4, issue 145, 1992 Apr. (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - Computer Technology Review.--Vol. 16, no. 7, 1996 July (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Buyers' News.--No. 1023, 1996 Sept. 9 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - Electronic Buyers' News.--No. 1024, 1996 Sept. 16 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - Electronic Buyers' News.--No. 1025, 1996 Sept. 23 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Buyers' News.--No. 1026, 1996 Sept. 30 (Box 232, Folder 9)
  - Electronic Buyers' News.--No. 1027, 1996 Oct. 7 (Box 232, Folder 10)
  - Electronic Buyers' News.--No. 1030, 1996 Oct. 28 (Box 232, Folder 11)
  - Electronic Buyers' News.--No. 1031, 1996 Nov. 4 (Box 232, Folder 12)
  - Info World.--Vol. 18, no. 36, 1996 Sept. 2 (Box 232, Folder 13)
  - Info World.--Vol. 18, no. 38, 1996 Sept. 16 (Box 232, Folder 14)
  - Info World.--Vol. 18, no. 39, 1996 Sept. 23 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Info World.--Vol. 18, no. 40, 1996 Sept. 30 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - Info World.--Vol. 18, no. 41, 1996 Oct. 7 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - Info World.--Vol. 18, no. 43, 1996 Oct. 21 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - Info World.--Vol. 18, no. 44, 1996 Oct. 28 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - Info World.--Vol. 18, no. 45, 1996 Nov. 4 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - Kidsoft., 1993 Winter (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - Kidsoft.--Vol. 2, no. 2, 1994 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - Kidsoft.--Vol. 2, no. 3, 1994 (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - Kidsoft.--Vol. 2, no. 4, 1994 (Box 233, Folder 10)
  - Kidsoft.--Vol. 3, no. 2, 1995 (Box 233, Folder 11)
  - LAN Times.--Vol. 13, no. 20, 1996 Sept. 16 (Box 233, Folder 12)
  - LAN Times.--Vol. 13, no. 22, 1996 Sept. 30 (Box 233, Folder 13)
  - LAN Times.--Vol. 13, no. 25, 1996 Nov. 11 (Box 233, Folder 14)
  - PC Week.--Vol. 13, no. 38, 1996 Sept. 23 (Box 233, Folder 15)
  - PC Week.--Vol. 13, no. 39, 1996 Sept. 30 (Box 233, Folder 16)
  - PC Week.--Vol. 13, no. 40, 1996 Oct. 7 (Box 233, Folder 17)
  - PC Week.--Vol. 13, no. 42, 1996 Oct. 21 (Box 233, Folder 18)
  - PC Week.--Vol. 13, no. 43, 1996 Oct. 28 (Box 233, Folder 19)
  - PC Week.--Vol. 13, no. 44, 1996 Nov. 4 (Box 233, Folder 20)
  - Compaq portable computer BASIC reference guide, 1983 (Box 233, Folder 21)
  - Cygnet Communications CoSystem Reference Library, 1984 (Box 233, Folder 22)
  - Sperry Personal Computer System Multiplan User's Guide, 1983 (Box 233, Folder 24)
  - Action Max Game Video: Hydrosub: 2021, 1987 (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - Action Max Game Video: The Rescue of Pops Ghostly, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Child World Children's Palace presents Video Toy Chest: a toy catalog on videotape, 1990 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Compute Magazine's Entertainment Software Showcase: video and audio preview of the latest game software, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - Data General Corporation Rich Little Promo part # 012-2480, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Data General / One; Tilt Screen / Foot Door: Upgrade Procedure, 1985 Mar. (Box 252, Folder 6)
  - [Mindscape, Inc.] Dragon Lore: The Legend Begins, 1990 (Box 252, Folder 7)
  - Electronic Arts TV Robot Rascals Video: Electronic Arts. Breene Kerr Productions., 1986 Sept. (Box 252, Folder 8)
  - [Fischertechnik Computing Teach-in Robot (for the Commodore 64) instructional video], n.d. (Box 252, Folder 9)
  - Game Player's Gametape for Nintendo Cartridges.--Vol. 1, no. 9: Power Glove, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 10)
  - Game Player's Gametape for Nintendo Cartridges.--Vol. 1, no. 12: Acclaim [Double Dragon I: The Revenge; Total Recall; Narc; and more top games], n.d. (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Game Player's Gametape for Game Boy Games.--Vol. 1, no. 13 [Batman, Double Dragon, Castlevania Adventure, Final Fantasy Legend, & Wizards & Warriors X], 1992 Oct. (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Games Systems Comparison Tape, 1992 Oct. (Box 253, Folder 3)
  - How to Score More Points on Nintendo Games: instructional video, 1992 Oct. (Box 253, Folder 4)
  - Introducing Children to the World of Computers, 1992 Oct. (Box 253, Folder 5)
  - News Flash / Rock & Roll Super Game Boy Promotion tape, n.d. (Box 253, Folder 6)
  - Super Game Boy News Flash / Rock & Roll: The making of Donkey Kong Country, n.d. (Box 253, Folder 7)
  - Point of Purchase 2 promo tape, n.d. (Box 253, Folder 8)
  - Sega Genesis / Game Gear merchandising video, 1994 Winter (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - The Breckenridge Caper of 1798 [Superior Software, Inc.] by Stephen M. Cabrinety. 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. [2 copies], 1982 (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Legendary Conflict [Superior Software, Inc.] by Stephen M. Cabrinety. 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. [2 copies], 1982 (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Quest for the Scarlet Letter [Superior Software, Inc.] by Stephen M. Cabrinety. 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. [2 copies], 1982 (Box 254, Folder 3)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 128: Disk 1571 [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 128: BASIC 7.0 [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Apple IIe: ProDOS Utilities [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Apple IIe: Grappler + with Print Shop [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Apple IIe: Imagewriter [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Apple IIe: Screenwriter II [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Apple IIe: Appleworks [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Apple IIe: The Newsroom [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Apple IIe: Applesoft BASIC (ProDOS) [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 128: C128 Mode Selection (2 copies) [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: Disk - 1541 [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: BASIC 2.0 [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: Sprites Only [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: Sky Travel [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: Simon's BASIC [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: Pilot [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: LOGO (sheet 2) [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: LOGO (sheet 1) [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: Flight SImulator II [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: Doodle [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - Leroy's Cheatsheet- Keyboard Overlay for the Commodore 64: COMAL (.14) [Cheatsheet Products, Inc.], 1986 (Box 255)
  - MicroPro Wordstar Professional Reference Manual for MailMerge Release 3.3, 1983 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. C-128 Mode Selection keyboard extender overlay [2 copies], 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. COMAL (.14) keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Doodle keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Flight Simulator keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Logo (sheet 2) keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Logo (sheet 1) keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Pilot keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1983 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Simon's BASIC keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1984 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Sky Travel keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64 for the Commodore 64, 1984 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Sprites Only keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1984 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. BASIC 2.0 keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1986 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Leroy's CHEATSHEET keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1986 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Disk - 1541 keyboard overlay for the Commodore 64, 1986 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Applesoft BASIC (ProDOS) keyboard overlay for the Apple IIe, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. The Newsroom keyboard overlay for the Apple IIe, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Appleworks (includes 2.0) keyboard overlay for the Apple IIe, 1987 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Screenwriter II keyboard overlay for the Apple IIe, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Imagewriter keyboard overlay for the Apple IIe, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Grappler + with Print Shop keyboard overlay for the Apple IIe, 1985 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. ProDOS Utilities keyboard overlay for the Apple IIe, 1986 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. BASIC 7.0 keyboard overlay for the Commodore 128, 1986 (Box 255)
  - Cheatsheet Products, Inc. Disk - 1571 keyboard overlay for the Commodore 128, 1986 (Box 255)
  - Sony PlayStation advertisement: "Sofia Says", n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Infocom Adventures, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Amiga DOS, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with SpeedScript 3.0, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with BASIC 7.0 [2 copies], n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with 8510 / Prowriter, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Commodore DOS, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Vizawrite, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Ultima III, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Compuserve, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with CP/M Plus, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Elite, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Easy Script, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Paperclip [2 copies], n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with BASIC Reminded and Syntax Checker, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Gemini-10X Printer control codes, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay]: code summary for WordPro 3 Plus / 64, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay]: Doodle, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay]: Superbase 64, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay]: Logo, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with F-15 Strike Eagle, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for use with Comal 0.14, n.d. (Box 255)
  - ERG Card [keyboard overlay] for Flight Simulator II, n.d. (Box 255)
  - Portrait of Stephen M. Cabrinety, August 4, 1996 to October 4, 1995. Finkle Photography, Leominster, MA. 1 art original: computer-generated composite retouched photograph [?]; 27 x 35 cm. (42 x 50 cm. with frame), 1998 (Box 256)
  - [Magnum Software.] Gypsy: The computer oracle game, n.d. (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Super Mario Bros.: This ain't no game [movie poster], 1993 (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Compu-Pedia. Monsey, NY: Abco Publications, 1990 (Box 258, Folder 1)